

ANA COLELL

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a fullstack developer based in Greece with strong communication skills due to my background in languages and former experience in the education and tourism industry.

Having completed Le Wagon Fullstack Development Bootcamp I am looking forward to continue learning amongst a great team in which I can make a meaningful contribution.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

ES6 Javascript React HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Ruby on Rails APIS, GraphQL, JSON, Scraping Relational Databases, SQL, Postgres, MongoDB Wireframes, Prototyping, UI Design Git, Github

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native **English Fluent** German Fluent

Working Proficiency Greek

French Basic

HOW TO REACH ME



+30 698 995 3890



anacolell8@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/anacolell/



github.com/anacolell

EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

Le Wagon Stockholm - Batch #612 **Web Development**

April 2021 / June 2021

9-week full-time intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on

Master of Arts in Teaching Spanish as a Second Language Universitat de Barcelona, Barcelona, 2012 / 2014

Bachelor of Arts, Translation and Interpreting Universitat Pompeu Fabra. Barcelona, 2007 / 2012

PROJECTS

Portfolio website

www.anacolell.dev

Personal website built with React and styled components showcasing all of my projects. The majority of them were built with React, MERN stack or Ruby on rails.

CAREER SUMMARY

Front Office Agent

Melia Vienna | May 2019 to April 2021. Vienna, Austria.

Translator

Terra Mater | March 2018 to May 2019. Remote. Translation and transcription of interviews (English <> Spanish) for the National Geographic documentary 'Sea of Shadows'.

Spanish and English Teacher

Aquea Weiterbildung | March 2015 to Feb. 2018. Vienna, Austria.